{
  "title": "Capitales del Mundo",
  "bg_color1": "lightgray",
  "bg_color2": "lightblue",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "España",
      "answer": "Madrid"
    },
    {
      "question": "Francia",
      "answer": "París"
    },
    {
      "question": "Italia",
      "answer": "Roma"
    },
    {
      "question": "Alemania",
      "answer": "Berlín"
    },
    {
      "question": "Reino Unido",
      "answer": "Londres"
    },
    {
      "question": "Japón",
      "answer": "Tokio"
    },
    {
      "question": "China",
      "answer": "Pekín"
    },
    {
      "question": "Rusia",
      "answer": "Moscú"
    },
    {
      "question": "Estados Unidos",
      "answer": "Washington D.C."
    },
    {
      "question": "Canadá",
      "answer": "Ottawa"
    },
    {
      "question": "México",
      "answer": "Ciudad de México"
    },
    {
      "question": "Brasil",
      "answer": "Brasilia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Argentina",
      "answer": "Buenos Aires"
    },
    {
      "question": "Australia",
      "answer": "Canberra"
    },
    {
      "question": "India",
      "answer": "Nueva Delhi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Egipto",
      "answer": "El Cairo"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sudáfrica",
      "answer": "Pretoria"
    },
    {
      "question": "Turquía",
      "answer": "Ankara"
    },
    {
      "question": "Grecia",
      "answer": "Atenas"
    },
    {
      "question": "Corea del Sur",
      "answer": "Seúl"
    }
  ]
}
